scentbird.com 2019-04-25

# Scentbird Monthly Perfume Subscription Box: Designer Scents $14.95

This is how we collect and use your information  
Last updated October 17, 2014

Thank you for taking the time to read our privacy policy for [scentbird.com](https://www.scentbird.com/) and other online locations such as Facebook and Twitter (together, the “Website”) and our mobile application (the "App") (the Website and App collectively referred to as "Site") offered by Scentbird Inc, (“we," "our," or “Scentbird”). This privacy policy describes how Scentbird collects and receives information about you through the Site and any off-line communications with you such as telephone, e-mail and personal communications ("Off-Line"). This Privacy Policy together with the [Terms of Use](https://www.scentbird.com/terms) govern your use of the Site and Scentbird's collection and use of your information both through the Site and Off-Line.  
Please read this privacy policy before using the Site. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. Should the privacy policy be revised, the date of the last revision will appear at the top of this page. The new privacy policy will apply only to the information collected after the revision date. We will seek your permission for any material changes in how we use your information that apply to previously collected information.  
By accessing or using the Site, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use the Site.  
In addition to this privacy policy, you agree that the following provisions in the terms of use also govern Scentbird's collection and use of your information: acceptance of the terms of use, social media, indemnity, disclaimers and limitation of liability; disputes and applicable law; and general information.

What we collect from you

When you provide us information about yourself to us, we collect it.  
We may collect information from you in a number of ways. For example, we may collect personal information from you if you choose to create an account with us, complete an online survey or feedback form, rate or review products, sign up to receive communications from us, email us, or order any products or e-gift cards. We may ask you to provide information such as your contact information (name, email address, mailing address, telephone number), age, gender, and product or the brands and products you use. If you purchase a product through the Site, we also will collect your delivery and billing addresses and credit card or other payment method information (type, number, expiration date, card security code). We will collect or generate information about your transaction history and interaction with the Site. Users registering an account also must enter a username and/or password.

How we collect other information

We automatically receive non-personal information when you visit and interact with the Site and can collect information from other sources. Scentbird automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser as well as through other analysis of the Site. We also may collect information using cookies, web beacons or similar technologies, or through third parties using similar technologies. A “cookie” is a piece of data stored on your computer. When you visit the Site, your web browser may store cookies on your computer, which will better enable you to navigate the Site upon return. You may use the Site even if you choose to reject or delete the cookies. Cookies also may be used by some of the other websites for which a link is placed on the Site.  
We may access information about you from third-party sources and platforms like social media, marketing or ad firms. The information we collect may include your username and connection services, age range, gender, interests, advertisement interaction and viewing data and unique identifiers like a mobile identification number. We may combine this non-personal information with personal information, and will treat the combined information as personal information.  
Scentbird may use Google Analytics to collect non-personal information relating to your use of the Site. Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics mainly uses cookies to report on your interactions on the Site and help analyze how users use the Site. For more information, including privacy controls you can exercise over how your data is collected by Google Analytics, or to read Google Analytics' privacy policy, please go to: <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>

Children and privacy

If you are under 13, please DO NOT USE THIS SITE.  
We do not knowingly collect information from children under age 13. If you are under age 13, you are not permitted to use the Site. If you are 13 - 17 years of age, you may visit, browse and use the information on the Site but you may not register an account or submit any personal information. If you are 13 - 17 years old, by browsing the Site you confirm that you have the permission of a parent or guardian to do so. If you are a parent or guardian and believe that we may have inadvertently collected personal information from your child, please notify us immediately by sending an email to [support@scentbird.com](mailto:support@scentbird.com)

Use of collected information

We use the information we collect to communicate with you, advertise and of course, improve our Site.  
We may use any of the information we collect from you to serve you, respond to you, provide customer service and improve the Site and our products and services, including:

  * process and fulfill your orders, and process payments;
  * alert you to new features, products, events, or services;
  * process and respond to your customer service request or feedback;
  * contact you about your account or profile; for example, we send all registered users a welcome email to confirm registration;
  * improve the Site and create marketing plans;
  * implement credit fraud protection and risk reduction measures;
  * make other marketing offers from our affiliates and marketing partners that we think may be of interest of you;
  * enforce the terms of service; and
  * for any other reason you provided the information.

Sharing with third parties

We can share and sell the information we have collected with others.  
Scentbird may disclose the information it collects about you to:

  * to our service providers, sponsors, suppliers, vendors and others who help Scentbird provide the Site to you;
  * our affiliates and to merchants, licensors, activity and event partners and sponsors, and other third parties for their own marketing purposes, such as to provide information to you about their new developments, special events, programs, services, activities, products, attractions, stores, promotions and sweepstakes activities, and other important information;
  * third parties to provide analytics or to confirm or update information provided by you;
  * third parties in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or disposition of all or any portion of Scentbird's business or operations (including without limitation in connection with bankruptcy or any similar proceedings); or
  * as otherwise authorized by you.

We also may share your personal information in response to a subpoena, legal order or official request; when we believe you have acted in violation of the [Terms of Use](https://www.scentbird.com/terms); to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud or potential threats; to exercise legal rights or defend against claims; or as otherwise permitted or required by law.  
We also may use, share or sell non-personally identifiable information with third parties. Additionally, we may take personally identifiable information and de-identify it and share it or sell it in a de-identified or aggregated form with advertisers, business partners, and/or third parties in order to analyze usage of the Site services on or related to the Site or others’ sites; improve our services; improve our user experience; or for similar purposes. We will not re-identify such data and we will ask our contracting parties to agree to keep the data in its de-identified form.  
If you elect to participate in any promotions, sweepstakes, surveys, questionnaires, or other events during your visit to the Site, the rules or terms and conditions for those events may indicate that your information will be shared with third parties with your consent. Please review the applicable rules or terms and conditions for any promotions, sweepstakes, surveys, questionnaires or events.

Opting-out of communications

You don't have to hear from us if you don't want to.  
You may opt-out of receiving future opt-in communications from us. You may change your preferences at any time by revising your account profile by un-checking the boxes for opt-in communications. You may also click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any emails you receive from us and follow the instructions provided.

Third party links

We are not responsible for linked sites.  
The Site may contain links to or from other websites, including. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. this privacy policy applies only to the information we collect on our Site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our Site or otherwise visit.

Updating your information

We don’t want to send your perfume to the wrong home. You must keep your information current and updated.  
You are responsible for keeping your information current. You may update your shipping information by logging into your account and making edits to the “Billing & Shipping” tab. .Similarly, you may update your personal information, password and subscription status by logging into your account.

Notice of California privacy rights

If you are a California resident you can ask for information about any of your personal information that we have shared. If you don't want us to share your personal information for direct marketing purposes anymore, you can ask us to stop.  
If you are a California resident and have provided personal information to Scentbird, you are entitled by law to request certain information regarding any disclosure that may have been made by Scentbird to third parties of personal information for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, contact us at:

Scentbird Inc.  
10 West 33 st #1030  
New York NY 10001

The request may be sent to the above address or to [support@scentbird.com](mailto:support@scentbird.com) and should specify that you seek your “California Customer Choice Privacy Notice.” Please allow thirty (30) days for a response. Scentbird is required to respond to only one request per customer each year, and is not required to respond to requests made by means other than through the above email address.  
We will not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes if you request that we do not do so. You may make such a request by sending us an email at [support@scentbird.com](mailto:support@scentbird.com)  
When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what personal information you do not want us to share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personal information or for processing this request.

Security

We try our best to make sure all our information is safe, but the Internet is not completely secure. Any transmissions you make over the internet is at your own risk.  
Scentbird uses reasonable administrative, physical and electronic security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information. No transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Scentbird to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect personal information, neither Scentbird nor our service providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the internet. Any such transmission is at your own risk.

Let us know how we are doing

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us at [support@scentbird.com](mailto:support@scentbird.com)
